https://horizondatasys.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Last Updated: May 21, 2018
We at Horizon DataSys Corporation (“Horizon DataSys”) are constantly striving to provide excellent service to you, our customers and business partners, while building a long-lasting relationship with you. To achieve these goals, we occasionally need information about you when you visit our website or support portal site.
When you visit our web sites, you might be providing information about your visit on two levels:
Statistics collected as you browse our Web sites.
Organizational and personal information you knowingly give us.
Because Horizon DataSys respects your right to privacy, we want you to be aware of how we handle this information.
Our Commitment to Your Privacy
Horizon DataSys assures you that we do not provide or sell the names and addresses of our customers to outside vendors.
Horizon DataSys does:
Safeguard customers’ information from unauthorized access.
Collect, maintain and use customer information as necessary to provide the most helpful and targeted products and services to meet customers’ needs (e.g. customer care or new products or services).
Honor customers’ requests to remove their names from our telephone, mail or e-mail solicitation lists in a timely manner. Just Contact Us.
Maintain confidentiality of customer information when undertaking projects with our partner or other companies.
Horizon DataSys has always valued your privacy, and we reinforce this belief throughout our organization. Your information will be protected as described unless the specific Web page says otherwise. If you have further questions about our privacy policy, please Contact Us.
Information this Site Gathers/Tracks
Statistics Collected as You Browse Our Web Sites
As you browse our Web sites, Horizon DataSys’ Web servers collect information about your visit, not about you personally. Via Web server logs, we monitor statistics such as:
How many people visit our Web sites.
Which pages people visit on our Web sites.
From which domains our visitors come (e.g., “yahoo.com” or “aol.com”).
Which browsers people use to visit our Web sites.
While we gather this information, none of it is associated with you as an individual. We use these statistics to improve our Web sites, to monitor their performance, and to make it easier for you and other visitors to use.
Organizational and Personal Information You Knowingly Give Us
Within our Web sites, you may be asked to give us personal or organizational information in order to purchase or receive information about a product or service. This information may range from your generic zip code, to your specific phone number, product serial numbers and control codes, account number, credit card number, e-mail address, organization URL, or mailing address.
Use of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks
Your IP Address and Host Name
Horizon DataSys’ Web sites log Host Names (or IP addresses when the Host Name is not available) for systems administration and security purposes. These logs are monitored and analyzed to maintain systems and information security and allow us to constantly improve the value and the availability of the Web content.
Registration Forms
We encourage all visitors to register with Horizon DataSys, although registration is not required, except for access to our premium content areas. The registration forms require users to give us accurate contact information (like name and email address) and references that help us better serve you. Your name and email address may be used to send you information about our company, product updates, special offers, and newsletters. To opt out of receiving communications from Horizon DataSys, please Contact Us.
Download Forms, Order Forms and Enrollment Forms
Our order forms securely collect visitor’s contact information and financial information (like your credit card number and other billing information).Contact information on the order form is used for order fulfillment and may be shared with our Partners or Resellers if that is necessary to fulfill your request. The information that we require in our order form is only used to process your order quickly and accurately. Your contact information will only be used to send you the product that you purchase and your billing information will only be used to bill you for that product. During the purchasing process, you may be given the opportunity to sign up for future e-mailings regarding our products, services, and promotions. If you sign up, Horizon DataSys will share your contact information with other Horizon DataSys partner companies only, not with other outside companies.
You may also be given the option of registering a profile with Horizon DataSys which would store your name, purchase history, and billing information to make it easier for you to shop and purchase products/services from us in the future. You may opt out of this feature at any time by changing/canceling your profile online.
Cookies
A cookie is a small, encrypted data string our server writes to your hard drive that contains your unique User ID. We use cookies to deliver Web content specific to your interests and to control access to restricted content. A cookie cannot be used to access or otherwise compromise the data on your hard drive. You can choose to change your browser settings to disable cookies if you do not want us to establish and maintain a unique User ID. Please be aware that cookies might be required to complete certain functions on our Web sites.
Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks
The information you submit may be shared with third parties if it is necessary to complete your request, provide you with access to downloadable software, or as required by law.
General Data Protection Regulation
Where the new GDPR rules apply, you can contact us to:
– determine If we’re processing your personal data
– get access to your personal data that we have
– correct any of your personal data that we have
– erase any of your personal data that we have
Information Security
We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. When you place an order, the information is encrypted using the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Links to Other Sites
Our Web sites contain links to other Web sites. Please be aware that our privacy policy does not apply to these other sites.
Opt-out Policy and Procedure
Our Web sites provide users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us (and our partners) at the point where we request information about the visitor. In addition, from within the www.horizondatasys.com and http://support.horizondatasys.com website. Visitors can unsubscribe to the various communication offerings at any time, by deselecting the vehicles they do not wish to receive or by opting-out of all e-communications. Please note that opting-out of all communications will suppress every piece of electronic information from Horizon DataSys and is not restricted to only the communications listed on the subscription center page. Additionally, visitors who wish to remove their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service can Contact Us.
Correcting/Update Policy
If you would like to correct and/or update your information, please Contact Us.
Oversight
If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please Contact Us. We will address any issue to the best of our abilities.
Changes to Policy
Horizon DataSys will occasionally update this privacy policy. When we do, we will also revise the “last updated” date at the top of the privacy policy.
Products RollBack Rx
Reboot Restore Rx
Drive Cloner Rx
Net Control 2
Custom Software Development
Quick Links Support Portal
Downloads
Web Presentation
Articles
Contact Us Sales Inquiries:
1-800-496-0148 option 1
sales@horizondatasys.com
Technical Support:
1-800-496-0148 option 2
Submit a Ticket
Copyright 2020 | Horizon DataSys Corporation       Privacy Policy | Terms of Use
MenuProducts CloseProducts CloseDisaster RecoveryRollBack Rx ProfessionalReboot Restore Rx ProDrive Cloner RxAccess ControlRollBack Rx HomeReboot Restore Rx ProAutomated PC MaintenanceReboot Restore Rx FreewareReboot Restore Rx ProRollBack Rx ProfessionalClassroom ManagementNet Control 2 ProNet Control 2 SmallClassGet PricingEducationalCorporateCustom Software DevelopmentDownloads & TrialsRollBack Rx ProReboot Restore Rx ProRollBack Rx Time Machine CloseHome EditionRollBack Rx™ Home edition
Is the FREE System Restore
utility designed for Windows PC’sProfessional EditionRollBack Rx™ is the instant time
machine for your
PC. Restore
your machine in seconds.Server EditionRollBack Rx™ Server Edition is
designed for Windows Server
OS’s and MS MultiPoint Server
Compare Products
Reboot Restore Rx CloseFreewareDesigned for public access computing environments such as schools, computer labs, kiosks, etc.Professional EditionPrevent any and all changes made on your drive(s) making those PC’s bulletproof and unbreakable
Compare Products
Drive Cloner Rx CloseDrive Cloner RxDrive Cloner Rx is a bare metal recovery utility that enables professionals to easily perform system backups, images, and assist with deployments.
Net Control 2 CloseSmallClassOptimized for small classroom environments for simple installation and configurationClassroomTeaching and classroom monitoring specially designed for k-12 and higher educationProfessionalAdvanced version of Net Control 2 classroom management products designed for large networks
Compare Products
PartnersDownloadContactBuy Now
